Finding Aid for the Waldo Salt Papers, 1936-1987
UCLA Library, Performing Arts Special Collections
Waldo Salt Papers,
1936-1987
93
Salt, Waldo
127 boxes
University of California, Los Angeles. Library. Performing Arts Special Collections Los Angeles, California 90095-1575
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE: Advance notice required for access.
Biography
Salt was born in Chicago, IL, Oct. 18, 1914; graduated from Stanford University, 1934; taught drama and music at Menlo Junior College, CA, 1935; began writing scripts for Hollywood films in the late 1930s; contract writer, MGM, 1936-42; civilian consultant to the Office of War Information, 1942-45; he was investigated by the House Un-American Activities committee starting in 1947; he refused to testify on Communist affiliations and was blacklisted in 1951; wrot e for television and films without credit, 1951-62; working alone or in collaboration, he added a number of important films to his screen credits including "Midnight Cowboy," "Serpico," and "Coming Home"; recipient of numerous awards including Academy Awards for "Midnight Cowboy" (1968) and "Coming Home" (1978); died of lung cancer Mar. 7, 1987 in Los Angeles, CA.
Organization
Arranged in the following series:
Produced films
Produced television programs
Unproduced films
Stage productions
Projects
Correspondence
House Un-American Activities committee
Professional activities
Personal materials.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of of material related to the career of scree n writer Waldo Salt. Includes correspondence, scripts, research, and personal pa pers. Personal materials include biographical information, family, legal, financ ial and medical papers, writings by and about Salt, projects not authored by Sal t, photographs, and artwork.
Access Points
Salt, Waldo--Archives.; Screenwriters-California--Los Angeles--Archival resources.; Blacklisting of authors-California--Los Angeles.
Container List
- PRODUCED FILMS
  - COMING HOME (1978)
    - Awards
      - Programs and tickets for Academy awards ceremony and Writers Guild reception, April l979. 5 items. (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Writers Guild of America: Best Written American Drama Written Directly for the Screen, l978. (Box 116, Folder -)
      - Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences: Nomination for Best Screenplay, l978. (Box 117, Folder -)
      - Hollywood Foreign Press Association: Nomination for Best Screenplay, l978. (Box 117, Folder -)
    - Clippings
      - Clippings from newspapers and magazines. Incl: interview with John Voight ("Rolling Stone", 5/31/79); articles on Jane Fonda and John Voight ("People", 6/26/78) and Ron Kovic (New York Times, 8/29/76). 7 items. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence
      - Legal correspondence with Jerome Hellman and Jane Fonda about Agreement to write, produce and release the film, l974-79. 30 items. (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Financial correspondence concerning distribution of film, 1978-82. 13 items. (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Legal correspondence concerning credit arbitration and other litigations. 25 items. (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Letters and notes regarding research, reception and special screenings of the film. 18 items. (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Congratulatory letters and telegrams for Academy and Writers Guild awards, April l979. 32 items. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Research Material
      - Tape transcript (2 tapes) of second interview with T. Hager, 1/11/74. 21p. (The tapes are in box 112). (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Tape transcript of interview with Al Riate, 10/14/74. 74p. (The tape is in box 112). (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Tape transcript of interview with Ron Kovic and Roger Steffens, 10/15/74. 71p. (The tape is in box 112). (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Tape transcript of interview with Haskel Simoniwitz, 10/18/74. 36p. (The tape is in box 112). (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Tape transcript of interview with David Carver, 10/23/74. 35p. (The tape is in box 112). (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Tape transcript (2 tapes) of interview with Bill Hager, 10/29/74. 32p. (The tapes are in box 112). (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Tape transcript (5 tapes) of interview with Bill Stroud, ll/5/74. 41p. (The tapes are in box 112). (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Tape transcript of interview with T.Hager, ll/6/74. 62p. (The tape is in box 112). (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Tape transcript of second interview with Ron Kovic, ll/8/74. 22p. (The tape is in box 112). (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Tape transcript of interview with Joan Anderson, ll/13/74. 5p. (The tapes is in box 112). (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Tape transcript (1 tape) of interview with Lydia McClosky, ll/16/74. 12p. (The tape is in box 112). (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Tape transcript (1 tape) of interview with T.Hager, 7/25/75. 39p. (The tape is in box 112). (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Tape transcript (1 tape) of interview with T.Hager, 8/7/75. 38p. (The tape is in box 112). (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Tape transcript (3 tapes) of interview with Grace Richell, 10/7/75. 2 versions, one incl. clipping from magazine. 6lp. (The tapes are in box 112). 38p. (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Tape transcript (1 tape) of interview with Wolthussen, 1/29/76. 2lp. (The tape is in box 112). (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Transcript of a telephone conversation with Martia Lindley, 10/31/76. 8p. (The tape is in box 112). (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Tape transcript (4 tapes) of interview with Roger [Steffens], n.d. 35p. (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - "We live the problems. We work the answers" (brochure), n.d., 12p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - Program of wheelchair sports event, Veterans Administration Hospital, Long Beach, California, October l6-l7, l976, 6p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "Camp Pendleton" (brochure), 63p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "Front Lines. Soldiers' Writings from Vietnam", 1975, 135p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "The New Soldier", ed. David Thorne and George Butler, 1971, 174p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "Ramparts. Vietnam Primer", 1965-66, 97p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "The Vietnam Veteran in Contemporary Society. Collected Materials Pertaining to the Young Veterans", May 1972, various pagings. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "The Pleasure Chest Compendium of Amorous and Prurient Paraphernalia Erotica, Et Al" (catalogue), n.d., 109p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "Sex and the Spinal Cord Injured. Some Questions and Answers", 1974, 44p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "Sexual Options for Paraplegics and Quadriplegics", 1975, 110p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "Wheelchair Bathrooms" (brochure), January l97l, 20p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "Redbook" (magazine), vol. 141, #1, May l973. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "The Wheelchair in the Kitchen", 1973, 32p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "Proceedings of Sixteenth Annual Clinical Spinal Cord Injury Conference, September 27-29, l967", Veterans Administration Hospital, Long Beach, California, 208p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "Paraplegic And Quadriplegic Individuals (Handbook of Care for Nurses)", l969, 64p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "Paraplegia news", vol. XXIX, #331, April l976. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "Paraplegia news", vol. XXVIII, #327, December l975. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "Paraplegia news", vol. XXVIII, #322, July l975. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "Not Made of Stone. The Sexual Problems of Handicapped People", 1974, 208p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - "An Introduction to Paraplegia" (brochure), n.d., 23p. (Box 21, Folder -)
      - Two newspapers articles on Ron Kovic: "The Best Years", The New York Times, August 29, l976; book review of "Born on the Fourth of July", The New York Times Book Review, August 15, l976. (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Photographic material, incl. 2 photos of unidentified American soldier in wheelchair, with Vietnamese children, (b/w, 6x9), and 1 photo of American soldiers and Vietnamese in boats (b/w, 9x11). (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Photocopy of course reader "The Psychology of Disability" by Barry J. Rabin, 1976, various pagings. (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - "Spinal Cord Injury Manual", n.d., various pagings. (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Articles, pamphlets, newspaper clippings and conference materials relating to topic "disability and sexuality". 18 items. (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Photocopy of typed article with interview: "Six Disabled Women: Survival Through Alienation", by Mimi Nelken, n.d., 18p. Article: "Mimi's World", by Mimi Nelken, The Philadelphia Inquirer, May 6, l973. (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Research on "Post Vietnam Syndrome". Incl. published and typed articles, clippings, letters, notes and memos, mostly concerning article "Vietnam Veterans: A Shocking Report on their Damaged Lives", by C. Breslin, "Redbook", May 1973 (folder 1 of 2). (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Research on "Post Vietnam Syndrome". Incl. published and typed articles, clippings, letters, notes and memos, mostly concerning article "Vietnam Veterans: A Shocking Report on their Damaged Lives", by C. Breslin, "Redbook", May 1973 (folder 2 of 2). (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Research on veterans. Incl. articles and interviews from "Penthouse","Playboy", "The New Yorker", "New Times", 1974-76. 24 items. (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Research on veterans. Incl. various articles from The New York Times, Los Angeles Times, "Rolling Stone", and various publications:"The Vietnam Veteran", "Civil Liberties" and "Focal Point", l973-76. 9 items. (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Research on veterans' organizations. Incl. material issued by the Vietnam Veterans Against the War/ Winter Soldier Organization (VVAW/WSO), and report on progress and activities by the Orange County Veterans Advisory Council, 1974-75. 8 items. (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Photocopies of typed surveys and questionnaires given to Vietnam veterans in l97l-72. 3 items. (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Various clippings and articles concerning veterans. Incl. film review of "Hearts and Minds", in "Vogue", April l975; photocopy of letter to Jane Fonda from Grace Rishell, March l974; and photocopy of procedures for naval funerals. 7 items. (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Copy of two articles by Catherine Breslin on veteran Bobby Muller: "One Kid's War" (12p), and "One Man's War" (14p); drafts and interview material, with corrections (various pagings), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Research on hit songs l965-69, dated June l975. Incl. billboard ratings (typed and hand-written), copies of lyrics and scores, unnumbered pages. (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - "Life" magazine, vol. 66-67, January-December l969, incl. index (Box 1 of 3). (Box 24, Folder -)
      - "Life" magazine, vol. 66-67, January-December l969, incl. index (box 2 of 3). (Box 25, Folder -)
      - "Life" magazine, vol. 66-67, January-December l969, incl. index (box 3 of 3). (Box 26, Folder -)
      - Magazines. Incl: "Life" issues: index 1968, 1970: January 9, April 3, May 8/ 22, July 10/ 24, October 23), "Esquire" (November l968), "Look" (December 1969), "National Geographic" (February 1967). (Box 27, Folder -)
      - Audiotapes of script conferences and interviews with Vietnam veterans. Labeled with names of interviewees, dated. (Transcribed in box 20, folders 1-17). 37 tapes. (Box 112, Folder -)
    - Script Material
      - Script: "Buffalo Ghost" (working title) [by Nancy Dowd], n.d. Heavily annotated and corrected [by W.Salt]. 227p. (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Notes on "Buffalo Ghost" script (7/25/74); preliminary notes (hand-written and typed) for "Going Home" script (working title), incl. extensive background notes on script and character development, and continuity notes, December l974-April l975. (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Continuity notes for ""Going Home", April-June l975. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Treatment for ""Going Home", 4/11/75. 60p. 2 copies. (Same as "Continuity Notes", Box 14-2, except for front page, "Treatment from Waldo Salt"). (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Outline notes for "Going Home", June l975. 65p. 2 copies. (Another version of Treatment). (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Two versions of draft, September l975-February l976. Incl. continuity notes and annotations. (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Draft, January-February l976. Incl. continuity notes, dated. (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Draft, February-April l976. Incl. extensive annotations and continuity notes, dated. (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Two versions of draft, February-March l976. Incl. continuity notes, dated. (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Master File, "Going Home" (working title), April-August l975. Script, incl. continuity notes, story conferences and notes on characters, dated. (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Master File, September l975-April l976. Script, incl. continuity notes and notes on characters, dated (folder 1 of 2). (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Master File, September l975-April l976. Script, incl. continuity notes and notes on characters, dated (folder 2 of 2). (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Master File, June-December l976. Incl. 1st draft screenplay, continuity notes and tape transcripts of story conferences, dated (folder 1 of 2). (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Master File, June-December l976. Incl. 1st draft screenplay, continuity notes and tape transcripts of story conferences, dated (folder 2 of 2). (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - 1st draft screenplay, 6/11/76, 147p. (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Draft screenplay by W.Salt and Bob Jones, n.d., 132p. 2 copies. (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Drafts for 1st draft, l975-76. Uncollated script materials and continuity notes, heavily annotated and corrected, dated (folder 1 of 2). (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Drafts for 1st draft, l975-76. Uncollated script materials and continuity notes, heavily annotated and corrected, dated (folder 2 of 2). (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Drafts and reworkings for 1st draft, September l975-April l976, incl. script and continuity notes with annotations and corrections (folder 1 of 2). (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Drafts and reworkings for 1st draft, September l975-April l976, incl. script and continuity notes with annotations and corrections (folder 2 of 2). (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Script continuity by Bob Jones, 12/27/76, with annotations by W.Salt. 6p. (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous hand-written notes -some by W. Salt- on script, characters and unrelated matters. n.d. 20 items. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - THE DAY OF THE LOCUST (1975)
    - Clippings
      - Clippings from newspapers and trade publications, 1970-75. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence
      - Congratulatory notes and telegrams to and from W.Salt regarding script, October 1973; letters to W.Salt from various universitites, with invitations, research proposals and other projects, 1977-l986. 16 items. (Box 80, Folder 11)
      - Legal correspondence regarding contract between Jennorah Productions (W.Salt) and Warner Bros. to write the screenplay, August 1970-January 1970. 6 items. (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - Eighteen typed letters by Ronald Shedlo -Warner Bros.- regarding research and script for "The Day of the Locust", September-December l970; manuscript letter by R.Shedlo, incl. clipping, n.d. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Notebook
      - Notes and sketches for "The Day of the Locust", incl. drawings, 1974. (Box 110, Folder 8)
      - Conceptualization of film's plot, characters and dialogue, on sketch paper. Includes both text and drawings. n.d. (18x24). 4 items. (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Publicity Material
      - Press-book and invitation to preview. 2 items. (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Lobby card, in Spanish ("Como plaga de langosta"), for Mexican distribution of the film. Inscribed on the back and signed "Rush, 8/24/76". (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Research Material
      - Reprints of photos from Warner Bros. Research Department, showing Los Angeles streets and buildings in the 1940s. 18 photos (b/w, 8x10). (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Typed notes on background information for script, incl. research on a major studio Art Department, Los Angeles in 1939 and N. West's biography. 24p. (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Photocopy of "The Natives Are Restless" (novel) by Cynthia Lindsay (n.d.), 223p. (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Photocopies of articles on Hollywood and Los Angeles, from newspapers and magazines, various dates. 39 items. (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Clippings from "Friday" magazine (l940) and "Unbelievable" magazine (n.d.). (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Audiotapes of interviews. Labeled with names of interviewees. 19 tapes. (Transcribed in box 13-1). (Box 111, Folder -)
    - Script Material
      - Chapter breakdown of "The Day of the Locust" ( n.d.), typed, 4p. (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Background notes on structure, characters and scenes, l97l-1974. 57p. (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Script, 6/26/71-8/3/71. 135p. (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Script, 1/8/72-1/16/72. 137p. (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Revised 3rd draft, April 1972. 114p. (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Master File, April-October 1971. Script, incl. revisions and notes with dates (folder 1 of 2). (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Master File, April-October 1971. Script, incl. revisions and notes with dates (folder 2 of 2). (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Master File, November 1971-January l972. Script, incl. revisions and notes with dates. (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Master File, February-April 1972. Script, incl. revisions and notes with dates (folder 1 of 2). (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Master File, February-April 1972. Script, incl. revisions and notes with dates (folder 2 of 2). (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Master File, February-May 1973. Script, incl. rewrite outline, revisions and notes with dates. (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Master File, June-July 1973. Script, incl. revisions and notes with dates. (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Master File, August-December 1973. Script, incl. revisions, drawings, rewrite and meeting notes with dates. (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Master File, December 1973-February 1974. Script, incl. revisions, drawings and notes with dates. (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Final version of edited pages, 1971-73. Uncollated, annotated, with dates. (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Uncollated script materials with annotations and dates, 1971-74. (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Transcripts of 6 tapes (#2 through #7) from scenes of script. (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Photocopy of storyboard, pages 2 through 39, with annotations. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - DOUBLE WEDDING (1937)
    - Script Material
      - Script, "temporary complete", 5/13/37. (W.Salt uncredited in this 1937 MGM production). (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - FLIGHT FROM ASHIYA (1964)
    - Correspondence
      - Letters from Harold Hecht to Yul Brynner and W.Salt regarding script, January-October 1962. 3 items. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Notebook
      - Notes and sketches for "Flight from Ashiya" script, incl. drawings, [1961]. (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Script Material
      - Script, 7/24/62, with revisions through September 1962, and scene breakdown, 134p. 2 copies. (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Notes, narration and pages of dialogue, with dates. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - THE GANG THAT COULDN'T SHOOT STRAIGHT (1971)
    - Clippings
      - Clippings from trade publications and newspapers, 1970. (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence
      - Correspondence with producers Ira Winkler and Robert Chartoff, MGM Studios and Jennorah Productions (W.Salt) regarding screenplay, writing credits and research materials, September 1969-July 1971. 4 items. (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Notebook
      - Conceptualization of film's plot, characters and dialogue, on sketch paper. Includes both text and drawings. n.d. (18x24) 13 items. (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Script Material
      - Rough draft, 3/19/70-5/17/70. Incl. background notes, arranged chronologically. (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Rough draft, 3/19/70-5/17/70. Incl. background notes, arranged chronologically. (Duplicate of box 3, folder 11). (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - 1st draft, 3/19/70-5/25/70. Incl. meeting notes, background notes and revisions, arranged chronologically. (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - 2nd draft, 5/27/70-6/10/70. 156p. (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Master File, March-June l970. Script, incl. revisions and background notes, arranged chronologically. (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Master File, June 1970-February l971. Script, incl. revisions and background notes, arranged chronologically. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Script, August-September l970, with annotations. 124p. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Revised draft, February l97l, with scene breakdown. 120p. (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Uncollated script materials, with annotations, l970-71. (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Uncollated script materials, with annotations and corrections, 1970. (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Hand-written notes in two notebooks, 1970. (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - "The Gang That Couldn't Shoot Straight" (novel) by Jimmy Breslin, 1969, 249p. Annotated by W.Salt. (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - MIDNIGHT COWBOY (1969)
    - Awards
      - Invitations, programs, tickets for Academy awards ceremony and other events. 1969-70. (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Screen Writers' Guild: Nomination as Best Written American Drama Adapted from Another Medium, l969. (Box 115, Folder -)
      - Screen Writers' Guild: Best Written American Drama Adapted from Another Medium, l969. (Box 115, Folder -)
      - Award from "Film TV Daily", l969. (Box 115, Folder -)
      - Hollywood Foreign Press Association: Best Motion Picture Screenplay, l969. (Box 115, Folder -)
      - Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences: Nomination for Best Screenplay, l969. (Box 117, Folder -)
      - Award from Office Catholique International Du Cinema, n.d. (Box 117, Folder -)
    - Clippings
      - Reviews and articles from newspapers, magazines and trade papers regarding release of film, Academy nominations and awards. l969-70. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence
      - Congratulatory letters and telegrams on release of film and Academy awards. l969-70. (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Letter from John Voight discussing possible project with W. Salt and Lindsay Anderson, March l974. (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence regarding W.Salt's copyright of screenplay and payment of profits. 1968-83. (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Letter by Dalton Trumbo, congratulating W.Salt on "Midnight Cowboy", 2/16/70. (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - Legal correspondence concerning payments made to W.Salt on profits made by the film, 1970-71. 12 items. (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Notebook
      - Conceptualization of film's plot, characters and dialogue, on sketch paper. Mostly text with few drawings. n.d. (14x17). 10 items. (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Photos
      - 12 photos of Academy Awards ceremony, 4/7/70 (b/w, 8x10); 3 photos w/ Golden Globe award (b/w, 8x10). (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Research Material
      - "Pageant" (magazine), vol. 23, #7, Jan. l968. (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Audiotape ( 1/4 inch) of improvisations by Dustin Hoffman and John Voight. 1 reel. (Box 113, Folder -)
    - Script Material
      - Master File, l967. Script, incl. revisions and notes with dates. (folder 1 of 2). ARCHIVAL COPY. (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Master File, l967. Script, incl. revisions and notes with dates. Annotated. (folder 2 of 2). (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Master File, l968. Script, incl. revisions and notes with dates. Annotated. ARCHIVAL COPY. (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Master File, 1967. Script, incl. revisions and notes with dates. (folder 1 of 2). (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Master file, l967. Script, incl. revisions and notes with dates. Annotated. (folder 2 of 2). (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Master file, l968. Script, incl. revisions and notes with dates. Annotated. (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Uncollated script materials with annotations, 1967-68. (folder 1 of 3). (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Uncollated script materials with annotations, 1968. (folder 2 of 3). (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Various notes: incl. comments on 2nd draft script by John Schlesinger, 7/18/67, 15p. (folder 3 of 3). (Box 3, Folder 1)